Kobato. 19 TL
“…White Christmas.”
To Mom
59 eyecatch}
Next Episode
“…Travelers.”
Kobato-chan, it’s all over the place!
Oh, sorry!
Did we get a Christmas cake from Chiroru too?
Yes!
Santa-san’s coming, right?
That’s right.
What’re you doing, Yuzuru-kun?
I’m making it so you can put lots of presents inside.
I’ll help too!
Ow, ow…
I-I’m sorry!
It’s okay.
Those are Santa-san’s clothes, aren’t they?
Yes.
Every year, Fujimoto-kun acts as our Santa.
Who else would do it?
That’s true. We’re counting on you.
I wonder if Fujimoto-san is still upset with me.
Dobato.
Yes?
Putting that aside, you do know, right?
The confetti, the confetti!
Yesss!
Kobato-chan.
Doumoto-san!
I've been waiting for you.
You must’ve worked hard today.
No, I’m fine!
I’ll walk you home…
…if it’s not a problem with you.
Not at all!
Thank you.
It’s so sparkly during Christmas, it’s wonderful!
That’s true.
Kobato-chan, is there something you want?
Something I want?
Um…
Well, thanks to the bazaar, I got some new toys…
Then, can I pick something out I think would be perfect for you?
A present.
For me?
It’s Christmas, after all.
What should I get?
Hey.
You look busy, even though it’s Christmas.
I’m fine.
I don’t care about Christmas.
Is something wrong?
No.
Kobato-chan?
It’s nothing…
Should we go?
See you later then.
Kobato-chan.
You haven’t made up with Kiyokazu yet?
I think I did something to make Fujimoto-san upset with me.
He’s different from usual.
He won’t bully me…
He won’t even look at me…
I see.
I’ve been wondering about that this whole time…
Kobato-chan, it’s not your fault.
I’m sure Kiyokazu knows that.
It’s just that he won’t admit it.
So it’s fine.
Yes.
Thank you.
It’s okay.
Mind if we meet up tomorrow?
Um, okay.
Then, I’ll be waiting in front of the preschool.
But it’ll be cold!
I’ll be waiting.
But…
I’ll be fine.
I’ll see you tomorrow then.
Yes…
It’s Christmas in the apartment too!
Ioryogi-san, I have to get you a present too!
What should I get?
Confetti! A whole bottle full!
I-I know!
Oh yeah!
I made this for you, Ioryogi-san!
Here!
Ioryogi-san became a reindeer!
Dobato!!!
For crying out loud.
I’m late!
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
You’re earlier than usual today, Kobato-san.
Yes!
We’re preparing for a Christmas party!
I see.
Kobato-san, if you don’t have any plans tonight, come to our place!
We’ll be having a Christmas party!
Mama’s making a feast!
You’re welcome to come.
Yes!
Thank you!
Good morning.
Fujimoto-san, if you’d like, come too!
To our Christmas party!
I’m working tonight.
And Christmas is…
Good luck at work.
Have a good one.
Now then, you need to get going too.
Okay!
We’re off!
Kobato-san?
Everyone looks so happy on Christmas, but Fujimoto-san only looks sad.
I’m sure it’s because I said too much back then…
It’s not that.
Kiyokazu-kun became an orphan on Christmas Eve.
Mom!
Are you all right, little boy?
I’m all right.
I see, that’s good.
Kiyokazu-kun's mother... never came home that day.
Not long after that, Sayaka’s father took him in.
Sorry for being late.
It’s all right.
Now let’s start the Christmas party!
I’m done changing.
Okay Fujimoto-kun, call everyone in.
All right.
Kobato-chan.
Yes?
Let's go once you've changed.
Kobato-chan?
Fujimoto-san’s a great person.
That’s true.
He’s a great person.
I’ll do my best too.
Yes.
Let’s all call in Santa-san!
Okay!
Santa-san!
It’s Santa-san!
Santa-san’s here!
Santa-san!
Huh?
Kiyokazu-sensei?
This is Santa-san!
Santa-san?
Is that you, Kiyokazu-sensei?
This is Santa-san!
Right, Santa-san?
Now then, what presents does Santa-san have for you all?
Santa-san, presents!
Presents please!
Thank you!
Thank you very much, Santa-san!
Now then, everyone.
Let’s eat the cake now.
Okay!
I guess I’ll go get a present too.
Fujimoto-san, good work.
I’ll finish the rest of the cleanup.
After all, it's Christmas, so…
Stop trying to look out for me.
Geez, why do I have to…
Save it.
Christmas is the busiest time of the year, you know.
You slavedriver.
Merry Christmas!
What’re you doing?
It looks pretty good on you.
Kobato-chan!
Kobato-chan?
I see.
Since it’s Christmas, Kiyokazu was holding it all in.
I think I made things worse and hurt Fujimoto-san, somehow.
Fujimoto-san must hate me again.
And that’s…
That’s…
Why does it hurt so much?
Does Kiyokazu concern you that much?
I end up thinking about him.
I don’t know why, but…
When I think about him, my chest hurts.
I see…
Doumoto-san?
Now I know the best present I can get you, Kobato-chan.
Thank you for coming.
It’s a Christmas present.
Don’t get the wrong idea.
It’s not for you.
I’d like you to give this to
Kobato-chan on the viewing platform.
Go. I'll take care of the work.
Wait, why should I?
It’s Christmas, yet she’s hurt.
So…
She’s hurt because of your attitude!
But…
Kobato-chan thinks it’s her own fault.
She keeps wanting to apologize to you.
She’s waiting.
She’s waiting by herself!
Fujimoto-san?
It’s not your fault.
You didn’t do anything wrong.
It's nothing you should worry about.
So, what are you getting so worked up about?
Um, do you mean…
Fujimoto-san, you’re not mad at me?
I’m saying…
I wasn’t mad in the first place!
Y-You’re mad at me now!
Anyway, don’t worry about it.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
I got this from Doumoto.
Um…
“Were you able to make up?”
“This is my present to you.”
“Sorry if he bullies you.”
Huh?
“Merry Christmas.”
Doumoto-san’s present to me is Fujimoto-san?
What did Doumoto tell you?!
He said he’d bring me the perfect present.
Doumoto-san…
He wanted me to make up with you.
That guy…
Hey!
Fujimoto-san, it’s snowing!
I can see that.
It’s so pretty.
haru ni saku hana
The flowers that bloom in the spring
natsu hirogaru sora yo
The spacious summer skies
kokoro no naka ni
Engraves and glistens
kizamarete kirameku
Inside my heart
asa ni furu ame
Even in the rain that falls in the morning
mado wo tozasu hi ni mo
And the day that I shut my window
mune ni afureru
My heart is overflowing
hikari wa kumo no ue
Because the light is shining above the clouds
yorokobi kanashimi
Happiness and sorrow
subete idaite aruiteru
I embrace them all and continue to walk
watashi no te to kimi no te wo
Take my hand in your hand
tsuyoku tsunagu mono
And make a powerful bond
The snow... really is pretty.
Yes!
watashi wo michibiku
Please guide me
Either way, when the winter
passes and it becomes spring…
tooi tooi yobigoe yo
O voice from the great distance
I’ll be parting ways with Dobato.
hohoemu youni
It seems like it’s smiling
utau youni
It seems like it’s singing
hibiku kaze no oto
The sound of the echoing breeze